Seyfarth Shaw Collection of Union Documents 6336
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seyfarth Shaw Collection of Union Documents
1950-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seyfarth Shaw LLP
6336
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Reports, constitutions, bylaws (administrative records).
This collection consists mostly of labor union constitutions, by-laws, labor organization Information reports (OLMS form LM-1), and labor organization annual reports (OLMS form LM-2). A few of the constitutions and by-laws are original documents, but most items in the collection are photocopies. Most strongly represented in the collection are the Teamsters and the International Typographical Union. The geographic focus of the collection is the Upper Midwest, center in the Chicago, IL area.
7623947
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 10, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Scope and Contents
This collection consists mostly of labor union constitutions, by-laws, labor organization Information reports (OLMS form LM-1), and labor organization annual reports (OLMS form LM-2). A few of the constitutions and by-laws are original documents, but most items in the collection are photocopies. Most strongly represented in the collection are the Teamsters and the International Typographical Union. The geographic focus of the collection is the Upper Midwest, centered in the Chicago, IL area.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6337: Seyfarth Shaw Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6346 PUBS: Seyfarth Shaw Labor Publications 6350: Seyfarth Shaw Newsclipping File
International Typographical Union; Seyfarth Shaw LLP; Teamsters
7623947
- Allied Novelty and Production Workers; Chicago Osteopathic Hospital Nurses; Combined Counties Police; Combined Labor Unions; Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers; IBEW; Fire Fighters; Flight Attendants; IAM; Seafarers; SEIU; Steelworkers (Box 1)
  - International Union of Allied Novelty and Production Workers - Constitutions and By-laws, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Osteopathic Hospital, Nurses Association -- Constitutions and By-laws (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Osteopathic Hospital, Nurses Association -- Labor Org. Annual Report, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Combined Counties Police Association - By-laws, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - United Labor Unions -- Constitutions and By-laws, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers - Constitutions and By-laws, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers -- Annual reports -- 1977-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers, Local 191, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents
    Annual Report
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers -- Annual Reports 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local Union 1031 - By-Laws (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 193 -- Annual Report -- 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - International Association of Fire Fighter, Local 1260 -- 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Form LM-3
  - Association of Flight Attendants -- Constitutions and By-Laws -- 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - International Association of Machinists -- Annual Reports -- 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1 -- Annual Report -- 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge No. 8 -- By-Laws -- 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge No. 8 -- Annual Report -- 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - International Association Machinists, Lodge 850 - By-Laws -- 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1202 -- Annual Report -- 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Seafarers International Union of North America -- Constitution -- 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Seafarers International Union of North America -- Annual Report -- 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Service Employees International Union -- By-Laws -- 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Service Employees International Union -- Annual Report -- 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Building Service Employees International Union, Local 4 -- Constitutions and By-Laws (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Building Service Employees International Union, Local 4 -- Annual Report -- 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Service Employees International Union, Local 79 -- Constitution and By-Laws (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Service Employees International Union, Local 79 -- Annual Report -- 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - United Steelworkers of America -- Annual Report -- 1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - United Steelworkers of America -- Annual Report -- 1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - United Steelworkers of America - Annual Report -- 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 685 -- Annual Report -- 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 4886 -- Annual Report -- 1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Teamsters (Box 2)
  - Teamsters -- Annual Report -- 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters -- Annual Report -- 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters -- Information Report -- 1959-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters, Local 20 -- By-Laws -- 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters, Local 26 -- Constitutions and By-Laws -- 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Teamsters, Local 26 -- Annual Report -- 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters, Local 26 -- Information Report -- 1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters, Local 84 -- By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Teamsters, Local 116 -- By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Teamsters, Local 116 -- Annual Report -- 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Teamsters, Local 299 -- By-Laws -- 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Teamsters, Local 384 -- By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Teamsters, Local 455 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Teamsters, Local 471 -- Constitution and By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Teamsters, Local 471 -- Annual Report -- 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Teamsters, Local 667, By-Laws (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Teamsters, Local 705 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1959-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Teamsters, Local 705 -- Annual Report -- 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Teamsters, Local 707 -- Annual Report -- 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Teamsters; Television and Radio Artists; Textile Workers; Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators; Tile, Marble and Terrazzo Workers; Amalgamated Transit Union; Treasury Employees (Box 3)
  - Teamsters, Local 710 -- Constitutions and By-Laws -- 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters, Local 710 -- Information Report -- 1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters, Local 710 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters, Local 743 -- By-Laws -- 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Teamsters, Local 743 -- Contract with SK Hand Tool Corp. -- 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Teamsters, Local 743 -- Labor Organization Information Report -- 1959-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters, Local 743 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters, Local 773 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Teamsters, Local 988 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists -- Articles of Agreement and Constitution -- 1971-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists - Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - United Textile Workers of America -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - United Textile Workers of America -- Labor Organization Information Report -- 1959 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - United Textile Workers of America, Local 200 -- Constitution and By-Laws (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - United Textile Workers of America, Local 200 --Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Textile Processors, Service Trades, Health Care Professionals and Technical Employees' International Union, Local No. 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1980- 1987
  - United Textile Workers of America -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1977-1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Local 110, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Constitution -- 1974
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Local 110, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1979
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Local 311 and 780 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Constitution and By-Laws -- 1953-1976
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Local 780, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1977
  - Tile, Marble, Terrazzo International Union, Granite Cutters Division 220 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1979-1981
  - Amalgamated Transit Union - Constitutions (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union - Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1987-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 241 -- By-Laws -- 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 241 - Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1043 -- By-Laws -- 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 517 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Local By-Laws and Contract
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 517 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - United Transportation Union, Local 768 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - National Treasury Employees Union -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Typographical; Viking Independent Union; Waterbury Watch Workers; Wholesale Newspaper Distributors; Wreckers and General Laborers (Box 4)
  - International Typographical Union -- Book of Laws -- 1968-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - International Typographical Union -- Book of Laws -- 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - International Typographical Union -- General Laws -- 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - International Typographical Union -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1975-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - International Typographical Union. Mailers Local 3 -- Constitution and By-Laws (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - International Typographical Union, Mailers Local 8 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 9 -- Constitution, By-Laws and General Laws -- 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 9 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1974- 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Typographical Union No. 16 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Typographical Union No. 16 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Detroit Typographical Union no. 18 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - International Typographical Union no. 81 (Mailers) -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - International Mailers Union, Local 105 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 125 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 177 - Constitutions and By-Laws -- 1957 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 177 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 194 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 221 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 221 -- Union Organization Annual Report -- 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 318 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 430 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 430 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 895 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1974 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - International Typographical Union, Local 895 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Viking Independent Union -- Constitution (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Waterbury Watch Workmen's' Union no. 24369 -- Constitution and By-Laws -- 1960 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Waterbury Watch Workers' Union no. 24369 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Wholesale Newspaper Distributors Association -- Constitution -- 1950 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Wholesale Newspaper Distributors Association -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Wreckers and General Laborers' Local Union 225 -- Labor Organization Annual Report -- 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 30)